(Leonard:)Women, men, the whole
sitting-standing deal.
(Leonard:)So what are we talking about?
(Raj:)Uh, my plans
with Priya.
(Sheldon:)He rejected Train Day.
(Leonard:)Did you make it clear that
it's two different train cars
turned into hotdog stands?
(Sheldon:)Abundantly.
(Leonard:)I guess he just hates fun.
That's what I said!
(Priya:)Okay, so... what's
new with you guys?
(Howard:)I have a girlfriend now.
Hey, good for you!
Yeah, I just want
to put it out there
(Howard:)in case I inadvertently
(Howard:)squirt any pheromones
in your direction.
(Howard:)Happy?
So, Priya, what are your
plans while you're here?
(Priya:)I don't know. I just
have the one day.
(Sheldon:)Do you like trains?
(Priya:)Not particularly.
(Sheldon:)You might as well just wait
at the airport for your flight.
"You are in a forest.
"There is quicksand to the west,
a path leads to the east."